https://www.decalcity.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Decal City is committed to maintaining the trust
and confidence of its customers and visitors to our web site.
We are also committed
to the security of the data we collect during the creation of new accounts.
That's why we want you to understand our commitment to protect
your privacy.
Decal City's account creation form requires users to give us contact information (such as their name, address, and e-mail address.)This personal information allows us to process and fulfill your orders, and customize your shopping experience.
Decal City takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously. All of the personal information we compile for your account is considered confidential. This information is protected by usernames and passwords. You should keep your password and user name confidential. We have implemented industry standard security mechanisms to protect this information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Decal City's software and hardware are configured to provide effective security.
Because your privacy is important, Decal City will not sell, rent or trade your personal information to anyone for any reason. Should you have a questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@decalcity.com
Back
Custom Decals
Windshield Lettering
Windshield Banners
Custom Names
Business Lettering
Boat Registration
Jet Ski Registration
Mailbox Lettering
USDOT Registration
Snowmobile Registration
Magnetics
Categories
Recommended ProductsStick Family DecalsAnimalsBirdsBugsCatsDinosaurDogsFishHorsesWildlifeATV & WatersportBusiness BordersBusiness GraphicsCowboy UpEquipmentFire & RescueHood DecalsMotorcycleNauticalPeopleIndianRacingSayings & PhrasesSemi GraphicsSlogansSports DecalsTribal Decals
Information
Contact Us
Request a Quote
FAQ
Decal Application
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
